How far would you go... as far as you dare.
Pleasure or Pain is a drama, thriller film directed by Zalman King.
A young designer falls under a man's erotic spell and is drawn into a
world of sexual abandon from which she may never return.
Victoria, played by Malena Morgan.
Jack, played by Christos Vasilopoulos.
Antonio, played by Daniel Sobieray.
Isabel, played by Kayla Jane.
Rita, played by Elle Alexandra.
Eve, played by Hayden Hawkens.
Pleasure or Pain is a 2013 erotic thriller film
written and directed by Zalman King.
The film was shot between Malibu, Santa Monica and
Westlake in California in the United States.
The film explores themes of designer, seduction, erotic movie.
The tone is emotional and intense.